Guide to the Office of the President Records, Alan Simpson Files, 1949-1979
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series VIII. Colleges and Universities, 1961-1977
  - Connecticut College, 1967-1974 (Folder 75.54)
  - Culinary Institute of America, 1971-1977 (Folder 75.55)
  - Duke University, 1969 (Folder 75.56)
  - Fordham University, 1974 (Folder 75.57)
  - Haverford College, 1970, 1974 (Folder 75.58)
  - Hillsdale College, 1976-1977 (Folder 75.59)
  - Kirkland College, 1968-1970 (Folder 75.60)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1969-1975 (Folder 75.61)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 1968-1976 (Folder 75.62)
  - Pennsylvania, University of, 1969-1974 (Folder 75.63)
  - Polytechnic Institute of New York, 1975-1976 (Folder 75.64)
  - Princeton University, 1969-1975 (Folder 75.65)
  - Rockefeller University, 1966 (Folder 75.66)
  - Saint Mary’s College, 1975-1976 (Folder 75.67)
  - Sarah Lawrence College, 1970, 1974 (Folder 75.68)
  - Simon’s Rock, 1967-1968, 1976 (Folder 75.69)
  - Trinity College, 1968-1977 (Folder 75.70)
  - Union College, 1969-1974 (Folder 75.71)
  - Wells College, 1972-1976 (Folder 76.1)
  - Wesleyan University — Middletown, Conn., 1968-1971 (Folder 76.2)
  - The Study of Educational Policies and Programs at Wesleyan, 1968 May (Folder 76.3)
  - Whittier College, 1970 (Folder 76.4)
  - Williams College, 1961-1968 (Folder 76.5)
- Series IX. Special Projects and Events, 1956-1975
  - Vandals and Vandal Worship — Correspondence, 1975 May (Folder 76.6)
  - Vandals and Vandal Worship — Correspondence, 1975 May (Folder 76.7)
  - Vandals and Vandal Worship — Correspondence, 1975 May (Folder 76.8)
  - Vandals and Vandal Worship — Extra Copies, 1975 Apr (Folder 76.9)
  - Minnewaska Minutes — Withdrawn, 1969 Jul (Folder 76.10)
  - Black Student Sit-In — Administrative Materials, 1969 (Folder 76.11)
  - Black Student Sit-In — Correspondence re, 1969; (17 folders) (Folder 76.12-17.28)
  - Lake Minnewaska II and III Minutes, 1969 Apr, 1970 (Folder 76.29)
  - MC — Attachments to the Minnewaska Conference Minutes (Folder 76.30)
  - MGJ (Glen Johnson) — Minnewaska Conference Minutes, 1968 (Folder 76.31)
  - GDL (George D. Langdon) — Lake Minnewaska Conference File #2 (Folder 76.32)
  - GDL - M.C. — List of Participants (Folder 76.33)
  - Community and partnership: Student Conduct at Brown University, 1967 (Folder 76.34)
  - GDL — Things to do at Minnewaska, 1968 (Folder 76.35)
  - GDL — Lake Minnewaska Conference Covering Memorandum, 1968 Oct 18 (Folder 76.36)
  - GDL — Minnewaska Conference “Joint Statement on Rights and Freedoms of Students” (Folder 76.37)
  - GDL — “The Wider Significance of the Columbia Upheaval” (Margaret Mead), 1968 (Folder 76.38)
  - GDL – M.C. — Student Conduct and Discipline Proceedings in a University Setting, 1968 (Folder 76.39)
  - GDL – M.C. — Parts from Cox Report (Folder 76.40)
  - GDL – M.C. — Parts from The New Radicals (Folder 76.41)
  - GDL – M.C. — Map (Folder 76.42)
  - GDL — Minnewaska Conference Covering Memorandum, 1968 Oct 29 (Folder 76.43)
  - GDL — Minnewaska Conference Discussion Guide for House Meeting (by Students) (Folder 76.44)
  - Minnewaska Conference Tapes (Folder 76.45)
  - GDL — Covering Memo of Reading Materials for the Minnewaska Conference, 1968 (Folder 76.46)
  - GDL — “Student Power — Response to the Questions” (Folder 76.47)
  - GDL — “Student Power: Myth and Reality”, 1968 Oct 13 (Folder 76.48)
  - Vassar College Student Handbook, 1968 (Folder 76.49)
  - V.C. Student Constitution (Folder 76.50)
  - GDL – M.C. — Covering Memo, 1968 Oct 24 (Folder 76.51)
  - GDL — “Final Report — Commission on Open Expression and Demonstration on Campus”, 1968 Apr 22 (Folder 77.1)
  - GDL — “Sindler Commission Report”, 1967 Oct 4 (Folder 77.2)
  - GDL — “Freedom and Order on Campus”, 1968 (Folder 77.3)
  - Lake Minnewaska III Minutes, 1970 Apr (Folder 77.4)
  - Articles — Minnewaska Conference, 1969 (Folder 77.5)
  - Minnewaska IIIa — Mr. Johnson’s folder, 1970 (Folder 77.6)
  - Education Law 129a and Legislative Hearings on it, 1970 (Folder 77.7)
  - Lake Minnewaska II — Original Mailing Packets, 1969 (Folder 77.8)
  - Originals: Minnewaska III Reading Materials, 1967-1969 (Folder 77.9)
  - MGJ (Glen Johnson) — Minnewaska Conference III, 1969-1970 (Folder 77.10)
  - Minnewaska Conference IIIa, 1969-1970 (Folder 77.11)
  - Minnewaska Conference — Working Materials, 1970 (Folder 77.12)
  - M.C. II — Grant of Authority, 1969 Apr 9 (Folder 77.13)
  - M.C. II — Parietals Legislation (Folder 77.14)
  - Review from November by Carla Duke (Folder 77.15)
  - M.C. II — Warning on Student Disorders (Folder 77.16)
  - M.C. II — Student as Nigger, 1967 Mar 3 (Folder 77.17)
  - M.C. II — Recommendations Related to Employment (Folder 77.18)
  - M.C. II — Minutes, 1969 (Folder 77.19)
  - MGJ — Minnewaska Conference II, 1968-1968 (Folder 77.20)
  - MGJ — Minnewaska Conference II, 1969 (Folder 77.21)
  - MGJ — Minnewaska Conference II — Minutes (Draft), 1970 (Folder 77.22)
  - MGJ — Attachments for Minnewaska II, 1969 (Folder 77.23)
  - M.C. II — Mr. Johnson’s Materials, 1969 (Folder 77.24)
  - M.C. II — Student Agenda (Folder 77.25)
  - M.C. II Student Records, 1969 Apr 3 (Folder 77.26)
  - GDL — Lake Minnewaska Conference File #1, 1968 (Folder 77.27)
  - M.C. — Minutes of the Minnewaska Conference, 1968 Nov (Folder 77.28)
  - M.C. — Minutes of a Meeting with the Four Chairmen of the Minnewaska Delegation, 1968 Nov 11 (Folder 77.29)
  - M.C. — Name Plates, 1969 (Folder 77.30)
  - GDL – V.C. — Minnewaska Conference Miscellaneous Items, 1968 Sep 19 (Folder 77.31)
  - Fox Proposal, 1971-1972 (Folder 78.1)
  - Year Round Operation — February Board Meeting, 1973 (Folder 78.2)
  - Year Round Operation and other Alternatives, 1973 Apr (Folder 78.3)
  - Director of Long-Range Educational Planning, 1972-1973 (Folder 78.4)
  - Year Round Campus, 1960-1972 (Folder 78.5)
  - Year Round Operation, 1973 (Folder 78.6)
  - Report on the Progress of Parietals Legislation (Folder 78.7)
  - Day Care Feasibility Report, 1972 (Folder 78.8)
  - Committee on Women at Vassar, 1972 (Folder 78.9)
  - Forward Planning Committee — Materials, 1968 May (Folder 78.10)
  - Materials Related to Associated Colleges or Poughkeepsie Area in General, 1968 (Folder 78.11)
  - GDL — Action Council of Poughkeepsie Report on Graduate Education Needs, 1968 Feb 19 (Folder 78.12)
  - GDL — Poughkeepsie “Blue Ribbon” Committee, 1968 (Folder 78.13)
  - GDL — Bundy Report (Xeroxed), 1968 (Folder 78.14)
  - Role of Education in the Mid-Hudson Region, 1967 Oct 13 (Folder 78.15)
  - GDL — Interinstitute Cooperation among the Associated Colleges of the Mid-Hudson Area, 1968 (Folder 78.16)
  - Vassar-Yale Newspapers (Yale Daily News), 1968 (Folder 78.17)
  - Men’s Education Papers, 1968 (Folder 78.18)
  - GDL — Confidential Materials on Future Programs, 1968 (Folder 78.19)
  - GDL — Calendar for Planning, 1968 (Folder 78.20)
  - Reports on Data Processing, 1964-1965 (Folder 78.21)
  - Graduate Center Clippings, 1971 (Folder 78.22)
  - Graduate Center, 1971-1972 (Folder 78.23)
  - Graduate Center — President Simpson’s Working Papers, 1971 (Folder 78.24)
  - Graduate Center — President Simpson’s Working Papers, 1971 (Folder 78.25)
  - Coordinating Committee — Graduate Center, 1971 (Folder 78.26)
  - Graduate Center — Candidates for Deanship, 1971 (Folder 78.27)
  - Committee on Graduate Center, 1971 (Folder 78.28)
  - Graduate Center, 1970-1971 (Folder 78.29)
  - Graduate Center, 1970-1971 (Folder 78.30)
  - Graduate Center, 1970 Oct 1-Dec 30 (Folder 79.1)
  - Graduate Center, 1970-1971 (Folder 79.2)
  - Graduate Center — Master File, 1970 (Folder 79.3)
  - Schaffner Report — Draft, 1970 (Folder 79.4)
  - Graduate Center, 1970 Jul 1-Sep 30 (Folder 79.5)
  - Graduate Center — Schaffner Report, 1970 Apr (Folder 79.6)
  - Graduate Center, 1970 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Folder 79.7)
  - Graduate Center — Supplementary Records, 1970 (Folder 79.8)
  - Graduate Center (Publications), 1969 Mar (Folder 79.9)
  - Graduate Center, 1969 Jul 1-Dec 30 (Folder 79.10)
  - Graduate Center — Publications, 1963-1970 (Folder 79.11)
  - Committee on New Dimensions — Copies of Minutes, 1966-1967 (Folder 79.12)
  - Report on Education of Men at Vassar — Interviews with Consultants (Folder 79.13)
  - Report on Education of Men at Vassar — Interviews with Consultants (Folder 80.1)
  - Student Questionnaire, 1967 (Folder 80.2)
  - Student Questionnaire — General Comment (Folder 80.3)
  - Student Questionnaire — General Information, 1967 (Folder 80.4)
  - Student Questionnaire — Response to Question #1, 1967 (Folder 80.5)
  - Wesleyan’s Proposal to the Connecticut Research Committee, 1967 Jun (Folder 80.6)
  - Ruth F. Sturm Letter, 1967 May 26 (Folder 80.7)
  - Revision of SUNY Proposal, 1967 Jul 13 (Folder 80.8)
  - Philosophical Discussions on Present and Future Vassar — Summary, 1967 May 18 (Folder 80.9)
  - Vassar-Yale Report, 1967 Sep (Folder 80.10)
  - Student Questionnaire — Weekends (Folder 80.11)
  - Sub-Committee of Student Opinion, 1967 (Folder 80.12)
  - Student Questionnaire — Dormitories (Folder 80.13)
  - Hampshire College — Working Paper #1, 1966 (Folder 80.14)
  - David Loeks Report — Preliminary thoughts on future work program, 1966 (Folder 80.15)
  - Innovation in Higher Education — Hillis, 1965-1967 (Folder 80.16)
  - Earlier Long-Range Planning Program Committee Reports, 1966 (Folder 80.17)
  - Letter from Dr. Nixon, 1967 Apr 24 (Folder 80.18)
  - Dr. Nixon’s Report, 1966 (Folder 80.19)
  - C. Gordon Post Letter — Proposals, 1966 Nov 18 (Folder 80.20)
  - Reading Materials — B. Currier, 1967 (Folder 80.21)
  - Copies of Questionnaires about Choice of College (Folder 80.22)
  - Robert A. Rossenbaum Letter, 1967 Apr 24 (Folder 80.23)
  - School and Society Books, 1966 Apr (Folder 80.24)
  - Map of Educational Institutions in Region, 1966 (Folder 80.25)
  - Preliminary Findings — Student Questionnaire, 1967 (Folder 80.26)
  - Student Questionnaire — Summer of Question #3, 1967 (Folder 80.27)
  - Student Questionnaire — Page 28 (responses) (Folder 80.28)
  - Alumnae Questionnaire, 1967 Apr (Folder 80.29)
  - Report on Questionnaires About Choice of College — from Clyde Griffen, 1966 (Folder 80.30)
  - Article — Graduate Schools, 1966 Oct (Folder 80.31)
  - Attachments sent with Minutes 7/21, 1965-1967 (Folder 80.32)
  - Mary Bunting — Forms and Some Answers, 1967 (Folder 80.33)
  - Interview — Polly Bunting, 1967 May 30 (Folder 80.34)
  - Mrs. Daniels Report on Degree Work, 1966 Dec (Folder 80.35)
  - Mrs. Daniels Memo on Coeducation and Alternatives, 1967 May 31 (Folder 80.36)
  - Post-Baccalaureate Education at Dartmouth, 1966-1967 (Folder 80.37)
  - Mary Dodd Letter, 1967 May 18 (Folder 80.38)
  - Jeanne Ehrhardt, 1967 May 17 (Folder 80.39)
  - Environmental Studies (Post Letter and Geology/Geography Proposal), 1966-1967 (Folder 80.40)
  - Environmental Studies Report, 1967 Jun 5 (Folder 80.41)
  - Clyde Griffen’s Report on Coeducation, 1966 Nov 18 (Folder 80.42)
  - Documents — Mr. Holmes, 1967 (Folder 80.43)
  - A New Dimension for Vassar College — Charles Griffin, 1966 Sep 15 (Folder 80.44)
  - Gelber-Ackley Report — Stony Brook, 1967 May 23 (Folder 80.45)
  - GDL — “The Education of Men at Vassar College”, 1968 (Folder 80.46)
  - Mrs Wislocki — “Package Proposal”, 1967 Jan 11 (Folder 80.47)
  - New Dimensions — Mr. Wilkie’s Memorandum, 1966 (Folder 80.48)
  - Admissions, 1966-1967 (Folder 80.49)
  - New Dimensions — A Report on Alternatives, 1967 Sep 1 (Folder 80.50)
  - New Dimensions — Miscellaneous Papers, 1967; (5 folders) (Folder 80.51-80.55)
  - Committee on New Dimensions, 1966-1967 (Folder 80.56)
  - New Dimensions — Curricular Topics, 1966-1967; (8 folders) (Folder 81.1-81.8)
  - New Dimensions — Health Services, 1966-1967; (6 folders) (Folder 81.9-81.14)
  - New Dimensions — Health Professions, 1966-1967; (4 folders) (Folder 81.15-81.18)
  - New Dimensions — Alternative Studies and SUNY, 1966-1967; (6 folders) (Folder 81.19-81.24)
  - Alumnae Responses, 1967 (Folder 81.25)
  - Vassar-Yale Study: Alternate Proposals, 1967 (Folder 81.26)
  - Supplements 1-10 distributed for first meeting of New Dimensions, 1966 (Folder 81.27)
  - Minutes — Sub-Committee of New Dimensions, 1967 Feb 14 (Folder 81.28)
  - Westcott-Ranzoni Report (Folder 81.29)
  - College Research Center, 1967 (Folder 81.30)
  - New Dimensions — Miscellaneous, 1967 (Folder 81.31)
  - Article on Stony Brook, 1965 (Folder 81.32)
  - Pattern for Progress, 1967 (Folder 81.33)
  - Articles on Residences, 1963-1967 (Folder 81.34)
  - Clark Proposal for M.A.T in Teaching, 1967 Jul (Folder 81.35)
  - New Dimensions — Computer Science, 1967 (Folder 81.36)
  - Drafts (Vassar-Yale), 1967 (Folder 81.37)
  - Faculty Elected Committee and Ad Hoc, 1967 (Folder 81.38)
  - Extra Graphs (Vassar-Yale) (Folder 81.39)
  - Fellowships and Graduate Study, 1966-1967 (Folder 81.40)
  - Freedman Reports, 1956-1958 (Folder 81.41)
  - Hudson Center for the Study of Man and his Environment (Folder 81.42)
  - New Dimensions — Inter. Office, 1966-1967 (Folder 81.43)
  - New Dimensions — General Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Folder 81.44)
  - New Dimensions — Inter-Institutional Programs, 1966 (Folder 81.45)
  - Letter — Mary L. Lehmann ’46, 1967 Jun 5 (Folder 81.46)
  - Mathew Vassar Complex and 5 ways of Educating Men at Vassar (Folder 81.47)
  - Sub-Committee on Alternatives to the Yale-Vassar Plan, 1967 Mar (Folder 81.48)
  - Notes to Committee on New Dimensions Prepares by the Request of the President (Folder 81.49)
  - New Dimensions — Off-Campus Experience, 1966-1967 (Folder 81.50)
  - Off Campus Experience, 1966 (Folder 81.51)
  - Pembroke College Report (Folder 81.52)
  - Discussion — Residential College, 1967 (Folder 81.53)
  - Syrett’s Speech — SUNY, 1967 (Folder 81.54)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1966-1967 (Folder 81.55)
  - Meeting June 15, 1967 — Hanford — CEEB (Folder 81.56)
  - Alternative Proposals — Mainly New Paltz — Meetings, 1967-1968 (Folder 81.57)
  - “Venture” Material, 1967 (Folder 81.58)
  - Purpled Notices — Sent with Minutes, 1966-1967 (Folder 81.59)
  - Letter — Mrs. Norman Rose, 1967 Jun 4 (Folder 81.60)
  - Working Outline for Committee on New Dimensions (Folder 81.61)
  - Wesleyan’s Proposal, 1967 (Folder 81.62)
  - Old Westbury Material — “Wofford,”, 1967 (Folder 82.1)
  - John Wilkie Letter, 1967 Jul 12 (Folder 82.2)
  - Working Papers — Morris Keeton, 1966 (Folder 82.3)
  - Working Paper: Undergraduate Education — Vassar College (Folder 82.4)
  - Vassar-Yale — Clippings, 1966 Nov – 1967 May (Folder 82.5)
  - Yale (Residential) Colleges, 1967 (Folder 82.6)
  - Yale — General, 1967 (Folder 82.7)
  - Booklets, 1965-1966 (Folder 82.8)
  - Joint Staff Meeting, 1967 Feb 27 (Folder 82.9)
  - College Guidebooks — Excerpts, 1961-1969 (Folder 82.10)
  - Coeducation Forum — Yale (Folder 82.11)
  - New Dimensions — Meeting Minutes, 1967 Feb 14 (Folder 82.12)
  - Yale Clippings (Folder 82.13)
  - Calendar for Planning, 1968 (Folder 82.14)
  - Candidates for New Ventures, 1967-1968 (Folder 82.15)
  - Non-Matriculated Students, 1968 (Folder 82.16)
  - Experimental College, 1967-1968 (Folder 82.17)
  - Forward Planning Program, 1968 (Folder 82.18)
  - Four School Study: Exeter, Andover, Lawrenceville and Hill, 1967-1968 (Folder 82.19)
  - Hampshire College, 1968 (Folder 82.20)
  - Housing Arrangements for Men, 1968-1969 (Folder 82.21)
  - Neglected Language Program, 1968 (Folder 82.22)
  - New York City Residence, 1968 (Folder 82.23)
  - GDL — Undergraduate Education for Men — Interview notes, articles, documents, 1967-1968 (Folder 82.24)
  - A College for Men, 1965-1968 (Folder 82.25)
  - Coeducation, 1968 (Folder 82.26)
  - Relationship with Poughkeepsie, 1967-1968 (Folder 82.27)
  - Reorganization Proposal, 1967-1968 (Folder 82.28)
  - Student Questionnaires, 1967-1968 (Folder 82.29)
  - Student Committees on the Trustees’ Proposal, 1968 (Folder 83.1)
  - Ad Hoc Panel — Responses to Department Chairmen Questionnaire, 1967 (Folder 83.2)
  - Committee on New Dimensions, 1966-1967 (Folder 83.3)
  - New Dimensions, 1966 (Folder 83.4)
  - Preliminary Report on Alternatives, 1967 Sep 1 (Folder 83.5)
  - Committee on New Dimensions Affiliation with SUNY, 1967-1968 (Folder 83.6)
  - SUNY, 1967 (Folder 83.7)
  - Mr. Rovetch, 1967-1968 (Folder 83.8)
  - Report on Men’s Education, 1968 May 1 (Folder 83.9)
  - Long-Range Planning Committee (LRPC) — Coeducation, 1966 (Folder 83.10)
  - LRPC — Calendar Reform, 1962-1963 (Folder 83.11)
  - LRPC — Public Service, 1966 (Folder 83.12)
  - LRPC — Teacher Training, 1966 (Folder 83.13)
  - LRPC — Vassar College (Faculty), 1962-1966 (Folder 83.14)
  - LRPC — Press Clippings, 1966 (Folder 83.15)
  - LRPC — Trends, 1964-1966 (Folder 83.16)
  - Committee on Long-Range Planning, 1963-1966 (Folder 83.17)
  - Preliminary Report on Alternatives, 1967 Sep 1 (Folder 83.18)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Student Questionnaires, 1967 (Folder 83.19)
  - Committee on New Dimensions (V.G.’s file), 1966-1967 (Folder 83.20)
  - New Dimensions Report, 1967 Sep 1 (Folder 83.21)
  - Vassar-Yale — Correspondence with Alumnae in re decision to remain in Poughkeepsie, 1967 (Folder 83.22)
  - Director of Special Studies, 1967 (Folder 84.1)
  - Alternative Proposals, 1967 (Folder 84.2)
  - Alternatives, 1967 (Folder 84.3)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Non-Western Studies, 1967 (Folder 84.4)
  - Institute of Public Affairs, 1967 (Folder 84.5)
  - Coeducation, 1967 (Folder 84.6)
  - Training in Allied Health Professions, 1967 (Folder 84.7)
  - New Paltz and Mid-Hudson Area, 1967 (Folder 84.8)
  - Stony Brook, 1966-1967 (Folder 84.9)
  - Yale-Vassar Study — Studies at other Institutions including University of Michigan, 1966-1967 (Folder 84.10)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Local Staff, 1967 (Folder 84.11)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Faculty Ad Hic Panel, 1967 (Folder 84.12)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Elected Faculty Committee, 1967 (Folder 84.13)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Administrative Organization (Vassar College), 1967 (Folder 84.14)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Committee on Residences, 1967 (Folder 84.15)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Admissions Questionnaire: Choice of College, 1967 (Folder 84.16)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Library, 1967 (Folder 84.17)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Departmental Representatives, 1967 (Folder 84.18)
  - Departmental Reports, 1967 (Folder 84.19)
  - Departmental Reports — Art – ESA, 1967 (Folder 84.20)
  - Departmental Reports — English – Spanish, 1967 (Folder 84.21)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Curricular Cooperation, 1967 (Folder 84.22)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Plans for Affiliation, Coordination, etc., 1967 (Folder 84.23)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Miscellaneous, 1966-1967 (Folder 84.24)
  - The Conference on the Liberal Arts College and its Future, 1967 May (Folder 84.25)
  - Yale-Vassar Study, 1966 (Folder 84.26)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Correspondence for possible follow-up in case of move, 1967 (Folder 84.27)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Legal Aspects, 1967 (Folder 84.28)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Meetings with Faculty Club, 1967 (Folder 84.29)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — First Reactions (Campus), 1966 (Folder 84.30)
  - Yale-Vassar Study — Campus Communications, 1966-1967 (Folder 84.31)
  - Student Participation in Vassar-Yale Discussions, 1967 (Folder 84.32)
  - Yale-Vassar Study — Correspondence with L. Bartlett, 1966-1967 (Folder 84.33)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Mrs. Eurich’s Correspondence, 1967 (Folder 84.34)
  - Material and Papers Prepared by George Langdon, 1967 (Folder 84.35)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Mr. Ritterskamp's Correspondence, 1967 (Folder 84.36)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Correspondence with Mr. Wilkie, 1966-1967 (Folder 84.37)
  - Cooperative Program: Short of Total Relocation, 1967 (Folder 84.38)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Budget: Carnegie Letter, 1967-1968 (Folder 84.39)
  - Calendar, 1967 (Folder 84.40)
  - Financial, 1967 (Folder 84.41)
  - Vassar-Yale Study Grants — Ford and Carnegie Foundations, 1967 (Folder 84.42)
  - Vassar Yale Report, 1967 (Folder 84.43)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Comparative Analysis, 1967 (Folder 84.44)
  - Coeducation, 1967 May 30 (Folder 84.45)
  - Vassar’s Philosophy of Education — Guidelines, 1967 (Folder 84.46)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Correspondence with Yale, 1966-1967 (Folder 84.47)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Site., 1967 (Folder 84.48)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Articles re Liberal Arts Colleges, 1967 (Folder 84.49)
  - Claremont Conference, 1966-1967 (Folder 84.50)
  - Vassar-Yale Report from the Joint Study Committee, 1967 Sep (Folder 84.51)
  - Vassar-Yale — Day of Decision and immediate Reaction, 1967 (Folder 85.1)
  - Vassar-Yale — Correspondence in re Decision to remain in Poughkeepsie, 1967 (Folder 85.2)
  - Vassar-Yale — Alumnae Questionnaire, 1967-1968 (Folder 85.3)
  - Vassar-Yale — Relations with Alumnae (General), 1967 (Folder 85.4)
  - Vassar-Yale — Letters and Acknowledgments (A-B), 1966-1967 (Folder 85.5)
  - Vassar-Yale — Letters and Acknowledgements (C-E), 1966-1967 (Folder 85.6)
  - Vassar-Yale — Letters and Acknowledgements (F-H), 1966-1967 (Folder 58.7)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Letters and Acknowledgements (I-L), 1966-1967 (Folder 85.8)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Letters and Acknowledgements (M-O), 1966-1967 (Folder 85.9)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Letters and Acknowledgements (P-R), 1966-1967 (Folder 85.10)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Letters and Acknowledgements (S), 1966-1967 (Folder 85.11)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Letters and Acknowledgements (T-Z), 1966-1967 (Folder 85.12)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Press Releases, 1966-1967 (Folder 85.13)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — News Stories and Clippings, 1966-1967 (Folder 85.14)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Meeting with Local Civic Leaders and other community reactions, 1967 (Folder 85.15)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Miscellany News, 1966 Dec 19 (Folder 85.16)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Open Letter to Alumnae, 1967 (Folder 85.17)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Draft letter to Alumnae (Not sent), 1966 (Folder 85.18)
  - Life Magazine Article, 1967 Oct 13 (Folder 85.19)
  - Alumnae Letter, 1967 Oct 2 (Folder 85.20)
  - Public Relations (Lydgate), 1967 (Folder 85.21)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Agenda and Minutes of Staff Meetings, 1967 (Folder 85.22)
  - Yale-Vassar Study — Joint Trustee-Fellow Committee, 1967 (Folder 85.23)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Trustee members of Joint Committee, 1967 (Folder 85.24)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Agenda and Minute of Meetings of Joint Committee, 1966-1967 (Folder 85.25)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Guidelines as Approved by Joint Committee, 1967 Jan 17 (Folder 85.26)
  - Vassar-Yale Study —Remarks at Joint Trustee-AAVC Directors Meeting, 1967 Feb 7 (Folder 86.1)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — President’s Statement to members of Executive Committee, 1966 Dec 11 (Folder 86.2)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Mr. Wilkie’s Summary Memorandum for Executive Committee, 1966 Dec 10 (Folder 86.3)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Miscellaneous and Unfiled Documents, 1967-1968 (Folder 86.4)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Mr. Simpson, 1967 (Folder 86.5)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Joint Staffs Meeting, 1967 Apr 21 (Folder 86.6)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Preliminary Report from the Joint Study Committee, 1967 Sep (Folder 86.7)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Unfiled Articles and Documents, 1962-1967 (Folder 86.8)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — The Revised Plan, 1967 Jul 31 (Folder 86.9)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Preliminary Studies of Inter-Institutional Relationships, 1967 Mar 2 (Folder 86.10)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Preliminary Report from the Joint Study Committee (Complete), 1967 Sep (Folder 86.11)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Joint Staff Meeting, 1967 Jun 1 (Folder 86.12)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Press Releases, 1966-1967 (Folder 86.13)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — President Simpson Speeches, 1966-1967 (Folder 86.14)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Joint Staff Records, 1967 (Folder 86.15)
  - Vassar-Yale Study — Joint Trustee-Fellow Committee Records, 1966-1967 (Folder 86.16)